We're going to talk about the board performance techniques right now and these are the four actions that your board can do that we'll perform on the snow.
The four actions are tilt, twist, pivot, and pressure.
When the board tilts, we're talking about tilting the board one way or the other using your feet and ankles.
Twist is when you actually can twist the board.
It might be tough to see on this because it's very, very stiff.
You can actually twist the board along its longitudinal axis.
Pivot; when we pivot with the board, we use our body to pivot the board this way.
Pressure, pressure is where you load and unload the board.
When I jump up in the air, when I land, I have a lot of pressure or if I lift myself up, just before I leave the ground, I'm unloading or unweighting the board.
Those are the four board performance characteristics.
Tilt, twist, pivot and pressure.